New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 4/6/00-6/19-00. (Box 15)
  - Working For America, 815 16th No. conf. Room, 5th Floor, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Jan 11, 3:30pm
  - NSSB Committee Meetings NSSB, 1441 L Street NW Board Room, Washington D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Jan 12, 8am 1 of 2
  - NSSB Committee Meetings, NSSB, 1441 L Street, NW, Board Room, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Jan 12, 8am 2 of 2
  - Joint Council for Political & Economic Studies Eighth National Policy Institute, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Jan 21, 2:15pm
  - Puerto Rico, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Jan 13-18
  - Lunch with Richard Winsten PD Ladds, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Jan 24, 12:30pm
  - Fiscal Policy Inst. Tenth Annual Budget Briefing Hearing Room A, LOB, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Jan 25, 8am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, Cornell University Medical college, 1300 York Avenue, New York City, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Jan 27-29, 1 of 2
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, Cornell University Medical college, 1300 York Avenue, New York City, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Jan 27-29, 2 of 2
  - AFT Executive Council, Miami, FL, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Feb 5-7, 1 of 2
  - AFT Executive council, Miami, FL, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Feb 57, 2 of 2
  - Jobs for the future, 88 Broad St., 8th Floor, Boston, MA, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Feb 8, 9a-3p
  - AFT Executive Council Wyndham Miami Beach Resort 4833 Collins Avenue, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Feb 4-7
  - AFL-CIO Winter Meetings Fairmont Hotel, 123 Baronne Street, New Orleans, LA, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Feb 11
  - PESH Press Conference, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Feb 23, 11am
  - Education International World Round Table, Brussels, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Mar 1-3 1 of 3
  - Education International World Round Table, Brussels, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Mar 1-3 2 of 3
  - Education International World Round Table, Brussels, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Mar 1-3 3 of 3
  - NSSB, Access, Diversity and Civil Rights Committee Roundtable, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - NSSB Executive Committee Meeting @ NSSB, Washington D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Mar 16, 12:15pm
  - NSSB Board Meeting, Isle of Capril Crowne Plaza Resort, 151 Beach Blvd., Biloxi, MI, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Mar 21-22
  - LMC Meeting, 4th Floor Conference Room NYS Workers' Comp Board, 20 Park Street Albany, New York, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Mar 28 10:30am
  - Labor Reps on the Workforce Investment Board, Crown Plaza Hotel, Albany, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Mar 15, 9:30am
  - Ruzzi Conference Call, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - The NYC New Paradigm Series Cornell Conf. Ctr., Room A 16E 34 Street, 6 Floor, NYC, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Mar 16, 5:30pm
  - AFT Vocational Education Task Force Meeting, Hyatt Hotel Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Mar 22-25
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Room 250, State Capitol, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Mar 27, 11am 1 of 2
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Room 250, State Capitol, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Mar 27, 11am 2 of 2
  - AFL-CIO/AFT/NEA Joint Leadership Conference, William F. Bolger Center 9600 Newbridge Road, Potomac, MD, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Mar 29-30
  - NYSTEA Conference Reg. Teacher of the Year Luncheon The Sagamore Resort, Lk. George, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Mar 31
  - AFL-CIO Immigration Forum, New York City, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    April 1, 9 am
  - Advisory Panel for Career and Technical Education, Marriott Hotel, Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    April 5, 10am
- Meeting Files, 6/26/00-1/7/01. (Box 16)
  - WIB Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    June 26, 2pm
  - Fiscal Policy Institute Board of Directors Meeting 100 S Swan Street, Albany, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    June 28
  - AFT Convention, PA Convention Center, Philadelphia, PA, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    June 30-July 7
  - AFT Vocational Education Task Force Meeting, Philadelphia, PA, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    July 2
  - NSSB Committee Meetings, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    July 10-11
  - NSSB, 1441 L Street, NW, Room 9000 Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    July 20, 11am
  - Democratic National Committee, Platform Committee Meeting, Cleveland, OH Sheraton Cleveland City Centre Hotel, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    July 28-29 1 of 2
  - Democratic National Committee, Platform Committee Meeting, Cleveland, OH Sheraton Cleveland City Centre Hotel, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    July 28-29
  - Democratic National Convention, Los Angeles, CA Century Plaza Hotel, Century City, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Aug 11-18
  - Meeting with Maggie Moree NYS DOL, Building 12, Room 425 Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Aug 24, 3pm
  - NSSB Meeting w/ Arthur Anderson NSSB Washington D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Aug 30, 12 pm
  - NSSB Board Meeting Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Sept 18-19
  - Stte Workforce Investment Board Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Sept 12, 11:30am
  - AFT Executive Council Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - National Institute for Literacy Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Sept 26
  - NYS Education Department Staff Meeting State Ed Building, Washington Avenue rooms A & B Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Sept 28, 10:30am
  - Career & Technical Education Conference Marriott Hotel, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Oct 2, 9 am
  - National Skill Standards Board committee Meetings, NSSB 1441 L St. NW Suite 9000 Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Oct 4-5
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Washington Court, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Oct 11, 9:30am
  - Nat'l Dissemination Ctr for Career & Tech Educ Adv Council, higher Ed Bldg One DuPont Circle NW Washington, D.C. Hotel - Jurys Hotel, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, Ithaca, New York, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Oct 26-28
  - NSSB Meetings Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Nov 3
  - NAVE Advisory Panel Meeting US Dept. of Ed., 400 Maryland Ave., SW Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Nov 3, 9 am
  - "Victory 2000" Reception, Grand Hyatt Hotel, Concorde Grill (Lobby Level) Manhattan, NY (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Nov 7 9pm
  - AFT Unity Discussions, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Nov 8 6pm
  - SWIB Meeting, Craftsmen Inn, Syracuse, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Education Conference, Holiday Inn Broadway, New York, NY, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Nov 16, 8am
  - Italian American Labor council annual conference, Sheraton NY, NYC, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Dec 1, 10 am
  - State Federation Conference, National AFL-CIO Capitol Hilton, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - NSSB Board Meeting, Holiday Inn Select Hotel, 480 King Street, Alexandria, VA, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Dec 7-8
  - US Department of Agriculture, Travel Disbursement Notice, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Dec 18
  - Hilary Rodham Clinton Swearing In Ceremony, Madison Square Garden Theater, Seventh Avenue & 32nd Street New York City, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Jan 7, 3pm
- Meeting Files, 1/10/01-7/16/01. (Box 17)
  - Education and Training Voluntary Partnership, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    January 9-11, 2001. Second Annual Decision Council Meeting
  - Cornell University, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Jan 16
  - NSSB Committee Meetings Holiday Inn select, Alexandria, VA, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Jan 17, 9am
  - fiscal Policy Institute Briefing, Assembly Parlor, State Capital Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Jan 23, 8:30 am
  - STW Legislative Planning Group Mtg. NYSUT, 159 Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Jan 24, 4-6 pm
  - Tanner Dinner, Museum of Natural History, Central Park West at 79th St. Enter Central Park West, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Jan 26, 7pm
  - NYS Alliance for Retired Americans New York City, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Irish-American Labor Coalition Dinner New York Hilton & Towers New York, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Feb 1, 6pm
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Wyndham Miami Beach Resort 4833 Collins Avenue Miami Beach, FL, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting Biltmore Hotel, LA Room - Westin, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Feb 10-15
  - NSSB Executive Committee Meeting Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Feb 21, 1 pm
  - New York Republican Congressional Delegation Breakfast, RHOB, Room 2253 Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Mar 1, 8am
  - Meeting with Maggie Moree & Greg Moreland, 111 Washington Avenue, Suite 600, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Mar 2, 1 pm
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Mar 8-9
  - Sons of St. Patrick's Dinner Sheraton New York Hotel 52nd & 7th Avenue, NYC, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Mar 16, 6:15pm
  - NSSB Board & Committee Meetings The Hershey Lodge, Chocolate Avenue & University Drive, Hershey, PA, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Mar 20-22
  - NYS Immigration Rally Capitol Steps, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Mar 28, 12pm
  - Capital District Labor-Religion Coalition Work Site Rally Albany Medical Center Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Mar 28, 3pm
  - AFT & NEA Health Care Conference Hilton Washington Embassy Row Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Mar 30 - April 1
  - Meeting with Cornell Univ. Staff and others, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Sales & Service Voluntary Partnership 3rd Annual Mtg. Sheraton Inner Harbor, 300 S Charles St. Baltimore, MD, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - National Policy Association, Fortieth Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    April 19-21
  - Dept. of Technical & Adult Ed Manufacturing Appreciation Luncheon, Atlanta, Georgia, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    April 19
  - National Research Center for Career and Technical Education Advisory Cnl Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    April 20, 9am
  - Working for America institute 2001 Annual Conference Fairmont Hotel 170 S Market Street San Jose, CA (Box 17, Folder 25)
    April 21- 24
  - State Workforce Investment Board Albany, New York 7 pm Board of Regents & SWIB Mtg., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    April 23, 1pm
  - NYSUT 29th Annual Representative Assemb. Rochester Riverside convention Center in Rochester, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - International Labour Organization, A New Tool to combat the Worst Forms of child Labour, ILO Convention 182 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - NYSUT's RA Annual Retiree Dinner, Lilac North Room, Rochester Convention Center, Rochester, New York, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    May 3, 5pm
  - Northeast council AFL-CIO Westin Hotel, Providence, RI, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    May 8-10
  - State School-to-Work Directors Omni Shoreham Hotel Washington D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    May 7-9
  - NSSB Board and Committee Mtgs. NSSB, 1441 L Street, NW, #9000 Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    May 10-11
  - Workforce Development Institute Board of Directors, Van Rensselear Rm. Crowne Plaza Hotel, Albany, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    May 14, 12pm
  - Alliance of Retired Americans Crowne Plaza Hotel, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    May 14, 1pm
  - SWIB StrathAllan Hotel Rochester, New York, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    May 17, 10am
  - AFT Northeast Regional Meeting Boston Park Plaza, Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Hilton Washington, 1919 Constitution Ave., NW Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    May 21-22
  - ARA Rally, Bristol-Meyers Squibb Bldg., 34 Park Avenue A 55th Street New York, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    May 23, 2pm
  - Protection Unions From Litigation: The Nuts and Bolts of Liability Avoidance, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    May 24
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    May 24-27 1 of 2
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    May 24-27 2 of 2
  - Unemployment Insurance Task Force Troy Offices of DOL, 2nd Floor, Troy Atrium, Troy, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    May 30, 10am
  - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - AFT Career & Technical Ed Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    May 31-June 2
  - New Alliance Convocation New York City, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - NYS Council of Senior Citizens Board Meeting IBT L. 237, 216 W 14th St. NY, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - CSEA Region 5 Summer Conference Bonnie Castle Resort, Alexandria Bay, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - US Dept. of Labor 21st Century Work-force Summit, MCI Center, Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    June 20, 8am
  - NYSUT Board Meeting, Desmond 6pm Ground Breaking Ceremony and BBQ, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    June 25-26
  - NYS AFL-CIO Pension Meeting in New York City Office, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    June 26, 12:30pm
  - Rally for Finch Pruyn Strikers Oakland Avenue, Glens Falls, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    June 27, 5pm
  - AFT Quest Marriott Wardman Park Hotel Washington D.C., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    July 12-15
  - The NYS Apprenticeship & Training Council conference, Georgian hotel, Lake George, NY, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    July 16
- Meeting Files, 8/16/01-4/17/02. (Box 18)
  - Clinton County Democrats, 2001 Salute to Labor, Elks Club, Cumberland Drive Plattsburgh, NY (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Aug 16, 6pm
  - finch Pruyn Rally Oakland Avenue, Glen Falls, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Aug 29
  - Colleran, O'Hara & Mills 9th Annual Golf Outing, North Hempstead Country Club, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Aug 30
  - Alliance for Retired Americans Leadership Meeting, Geo. Many Venter, Silver Springs, MD, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Sept 5-7, 1pm
  - State Workforce Investment Board The Desmond, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Labor Day Parade Breakfast, Tavern-on-the-Green, Central Park West @ 67th Street, New York City, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NSSB Board and Committee Meetings 1441 L Street, NW, 9000, Washington, DC Room Madison Hotel, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Sept 19
  - National Research Center and National Dissemination Center Advisory Council, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Oct, 8:30a-4:30p
  - National Dissemination Center, Univ. of Minnesota, CTE Regional Conference, Denver, Colo., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Oct 4-6
  - The NYS Leadership Roundtable Conf Marriott East Side, 525 Lexington Avenue, NYC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Oct 10, 9am
  - Nave Meeting (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Oct 11-12
  - NYS Labor-Religion Coalition Best Western Albany Airport Inn 200 Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - NSSB Executive Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Nov 6
  - Bruno Meeting, Sheraton NY, NYC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Oct 16, 10am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Mayflower Hotel, 1127 CT Ave., NW Washington, DC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Oct 16, 9:30am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Oct 18-20
  - Workforce Development Center Presidents & Coordinators, 100 S Swan Street Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Oct 24, 8:30am
  - Statewide Senior Action Council, Inc. 30th Annual Convention, Best Western Sovereign Hotel, 1228 Western Ave, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Oct 24, 12pm
  - Labor Religion Coalition dinner Schuyler Inn, Menands, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Oct 25, 6 pm
  - Labor Arts Advisory Board Meeting Shelley & Donald Rubin Foundation 115 Fifth Avenue, 7th Floor, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Oct 26, 11am
  - Steve Zahurak Class, HVCC, Brahman Building, room 204, Troy, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Oct 29, 6pm
  - Regents Public Policy Conference NYS Education department 89 Washington Ave, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Nov 7
  - National Policy Assoc. Comm on New American Realities, Musueam of TV & Radio, 25 West 52nd Street, NYC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - National Policy Assoc Comm on New American Realities, Museum of TV & Radio 25 West 52nd Street, NYC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Nov 8-9 2 of 2
  - ICT Symposium, Copenhagen, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Nov 14-16
  - AFL-CIO Convention, Paris/Bally's Las Vegas, NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Dec 1-7
  - NSSB Meeting and Executive Comm Mtg. 1441 L Street, NW, Suite 9000 Washington, DC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Dec 7
  - AFL-CIO Conference Call Re: 202 State Issues Agenda, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, Sheraton New York & Towers, NYC, Royal Ballroom B, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    Dec 18, 10am
  - Labor Arts Meeting, Rubin Foundation 115 Fifth Avenue (Bet. 18-19 Sts) 7th Floor, New York City, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Dec 18, 4pm
  - Northeast Council, AFL-CIO Meeting Condado Plaza Hotel & Casino San Juan Puerto Rico, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Jan 10- 16
  - OVAE Preparing America's Future Outreach Meeting, 400 Maryland Ave., Room 1W108, Washington, DC, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Jan 16, 8:30
  - The National Leadership Institute Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Jan 16, 3 p
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Holiday Inn Turf Hotel, 205 Wolf Road Albany, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Jan 17, 10am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Cornell U Weill Medical College 1300 York Avenue, NYC Room - Sheraton, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Jan 24-26
  - AFT Meeting, Wyndham, Miami, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Feb 2-4
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting Public Fund Trustees Roundtable Fairmont Hotel, New Orleans, LA, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Fairmont Hotel, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    Feb 24-27
  - Betsy Brand Meeting Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    Mar 4
  - PS21 Breakfast, Holiday Turf, Albany, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    Mar 6, 8:15am
  - NYC Central Labor Council's Disting. Service Awards Dinner, Waldorf Astoria New York City, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Mar 9, 5pm
  - Alliance for Retired Americans Washington Court Hotel, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    Mar 12, 11am
  - ILR Outreach/Extension Land Grant Panel ILR Conference Center, Room 105, Cornell university, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Mar 13, 2:30-4p
  - Mtg. w/ Ass't Sec Carol D'Amico, 330 C Street, S.W., Room 4090, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    Mar 13, 8:30am
  - NSSB Meetings, 1441 L Street, NW Room 9000, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    Mar 13-14, 12:15pm
  - National Institute for Literacy 1775 I Street NW, Suite 730 Washington, DC 20006, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    Mar 13, 9am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    Mar 14-15
  - SWIB Meeting, Strathallen Hotel, Rochester, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    Mar 21, 10am
  - NYSDOL Commemorates the Triangle Shirtwaist Company Fire Ceremony, North Lobby Concourse Level, Empire State Plaza, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    Mar 25, 1pm
  - ILR Outreach/Extension Land Grant Panel ILR Conference Center, Room 205 Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    April 9, 1- 3pm
  - NAVE Advisory Panel Meeting Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    April 10-11
  - Committee on New American Realities Westin Fairfax, 2100 Massachusetts Ave Washington, D.C., 2002 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    April 11-12
  - 2002 AFL-CIO/UALE Conference Wilshire Grand, 930 Wilshire Blvd. Los Angeles, CA (Box 18, Folder 53)
    April 11-14
  - ILR Outreach/Extension Land Grant Panel ILR Conference Center, Room 205, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    April 17, 9-11m
- Meeting Files, 4/19/02-10/19/02. (Box 19)
  - Working for American Institute WIB Training Workshops, Crowne Plaza, Philadelphia, PA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    April 19-20
  - American Youth Policy Forum, Perkins Reauth. Dis. Group, AFT, 555 New Jersey Ave., Ninth Floor Conference Room, Wash, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    April 25, 10am
  - NYSUT RA, NY Hilton, NYC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    April 25-28
  - Northeast Council Spring Meeting, Boston, MA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee for the National Research Center for career and Tech Education & the Nat'l Dissemination Ctr for Career & Tech Ed, Jurys Hotel, Wash, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    May 3, 8:30am
  - NYS Disability Mentoring Day 2002 Adoptive Solutions Institute 110 William Street, 9th Floor (Box 19, Folder 6)
    May 6, 4pm
  - Cardinal's Committee Dinner, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    May 10
  - Cornell ILR Land Grant Panel, Metro Office Cornell, 16 E. 34th Street, Conference Center, 6th Floor, NYC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    May 17, 3 pm
  - Northeast Council AFL-CIO Park Plaza Hotel, Boston, MA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Albert Shanker Lecture, Hilton Washington, Ballroom West, 1919 Connecticut Avenue, NW Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    May 15
  - Minnesota AFL-CIO New Alliance, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    May 20
  - 9th Annual Hole in the Walla Gang Camp Golf Outing, N. Hempstead Country Club Port Washington, NY, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - National AFL-CIO General Board Mtg. Sheraton NY and Towers, NYC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - McQuay Memorial, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    May 21
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    May 23-26
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Workforce Development Video Conference, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 48th Annual National Security, US Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, PA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    June 3-7
  - 48th Annual National Security Seminar, US Army War college, Carlisle Barracks, PA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    June 3-7, 2 of 2
  - AFT Voc Ed Committee, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Capitol Hill, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    June 13-15, 1 of 2
  - AFT Voc Ed Committee, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Capitol Hill, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    June 13-15 2 of 2
  - NYS AFL-CIO Task Force on Prescription Drugs, Westminster Presbyterian Church 85 chestnut Street, Albany, NY, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    June 17, 9am
  - Meeting @ Consortium & Mass AFL-CIO New York City, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    June 26, 10:30am
  - AFT Convention 2002, Las Vegas Hilton, Las Vegas, NV (Box 19, Folder 24)
    July 13-19, 1 of 2
  - AFT Convention 2002, Las Vegas Hilton, Las Vegas, NV (Box 19, Folder 25)
    July 13-19, 2 of 2
  - American Youth Policy Forum Roundtable Holiday Inn Capitol, 550 C Street, SW Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    July 23, 8:30am
  - Special Olympics Summer Golf Classic Oak Hill Country Club, Rochester, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council The Mountain View Grand Hotel Whitefield, NH, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    July 31-aug 1
  - Special Olympics NY Summer Golf Classic Oak Hill Country Club, Rochester, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Aug 7, 8:30am
  - Alliance for Retired Americans National Meeting, Hilton Washington Hotel 1919 Connecticut Avenue, Washington DC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Sept 3-5
  - ARA (Box 19, Folder 31)
    September 19
  - Local Jobs for Local People Community Awareness Demonstration, Shoppes at Wilton, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    Sept 10, 4pm
  - SWIB, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Africa, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    Sept.-Oct.
  - Africa, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    Sept. Oct.
  - Porter Scholars Judges Review, Lobby Conference Room, AFT Headquarters, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - National Institute for Literacy 1775 I Street, NW, Suite 730 Washington DC, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    Oct 9, 9am